paqoo.com 2011-01-12

# Privacy Policy - Home Design | Decorating Ideas | Gardening - Gallery of Home Design, Decorating Ideas and Gardening

Privacy Policy  
Home Design | Decorating Ideas| Gardening (Paqoo Dot Com) Privacy Statement

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all Paqoo Dot Com websites (a.k.a. blogs) including all the websites run under the Paqoo Dot Com domain. Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our contact form.

Email Addresses

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don’t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

Comments/Message Boards

Most Paqoo Dot Com websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

Cookies and Web Beacons

Paqoo Dot Com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Infolinks, Chitika, Kontera.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Paqoo Dot Com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Traffic Reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

Legal Proceedings

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Paqoo Dot Com may need to disclose information when required by law.

Business Transitions

If Paqoo Dot Com is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

Links

Paqoo Dot Com websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Paqoo Dot Com

Notification of Changes

When Paqoo Dot Com makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

Update – 04/03/2009

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
